coolblackberrythemes.com 2010-11-15

# Privacy Notice : Cool BlackBerry Themes

Cool Blackberry Themes is committed to protecting the privacy of our users and customers. We consider the security of personal information to be of the highest importance, and have established standards to maintain and guard against unauthorized access to user information. The following privacy policy outlines how Cool Blackberry Themes collects personal information and what we do with the information once it is collected. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This privacy policy applies to personal information collected on websites owned and operated by Cool Blackberry Themes It applies only to personal information collected on and after the date that this privacy policy is posted. 

**WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

**Information You Provide Us**

While we do not require any personal information to visit our website, we may at times request some personal information, such as your e-mail address, in order to provide updates about our products and services and our websites. We may also ask visitors to indicate if they would like to receive updates from Cool Blackberry Themes or its divisions, and if so, what types of information they would like to receive. Some areas of our sites are restricted and require login information (such as user name and password) to be created and/or entered at some point in the visit. Finally, our sites contain retail areas that require the entry of personal and financial information such as first and last name, credit card information, and billing address information. In summary, we may request and may or may not store any of the following pieces of personal information depending on the nature of the visit to our sites: 

  * e-mail address
  * user name/alias
  * password
  * communication preferences (topics of interest, type of communication, etc.)
  * first/last name
  * credit card information (type, account number, expiry date, etc.)
  * billing address information
  * phone number

We may also occasionally request non-personal information such as your phone platform, carrier, age group, gender, and other information that may or may not be associated with your personal information. 

**Information We Collect Through Technology**

We collect certain types of information as part of our normal website operations using a variety of technologies, including: 

**Server Logs**

When you visit our website, our web servers automatically collect information about each transaction between your device and our servers. This is a practice common to all web servers known as server logging. Server logs can contain, but are not limited to, your IP address (a number associated with your internet service provider, company, or educational institution), transaction date, browser type, request type (GET or POST), session IDs, and cookie information. This information is normally used to generate information about general usage on our site and to improve our website. It may or may not be associated with your personal information. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are files stored on your computer by websites that you visit. You can control, using your browser’s preferences, how cookies are treated, which sites may use them on your device, and how you are notified of their use. We use cookies for various purposes on our websites to enhance user experience and to provide information about general usage trends on our site. 

**Other Types Of Information We May Collect**

We reserve the right to request other types of information in the future. 

**What We Do With Personal Information**

Cool Blackberry Themes is committed to maintaining the privacy of our visitors and customers. Personal information that we collect either actively or passively from our visitors and customers is used only to conduct business, communicate with visitors and customers, improve our products and services, and improve our websites. In that regard, we may use personal information to send notifications or updates regarding the products and services of Cool Blackberry Themes using electronic or non-electronic means. You may request that Cool Blackberry Themes does not use your personal information to contact you by sending such a request to [jennifer@coolblackberrythemes.com](mailto:jennifer@coolblackberrythemes.com) or by contacting us at the below mailing address. Additionally, newsletters and product notifications sent by Cool Blackberry Themes. include unsubscribe information which will remove you from all mailing lists permanently or until such time as you request this status to be changed. 

Cool Blackberry Themes will not sell, trade, share, or in any way communicate personal information we store about you with any third party without your permission, with certain exceptions (see Exceptions, below). In the event that this policy is forced to change, such as a merger of Cool Blackberry Themes with another entity or the purchase of  Cool Blackberry Themes assets by a third party, we will notify you 30 days advance of this event, during which time you may contact us with a request to change or delete personal information that we have stored, providing that this information is not required for normal business and accounting purposes. 

**Exceptions**

Certain exceptions apply to our policy of sharing personal information with third parties. 

**Business Transactions**

In order to conduct business transactions on our retail websites, we must transmit purchase information to a third-party for credit card processing. We may also transmit device information to third-party vendors of products sold through Cool Blackberry Themes retail sites. We are committed to working only with reputable third-parties for these services, but are not responsible for the storing, maintenance, or protection of personal information by third parties once the information leaves our systems. By using our retail sites you acknowledge that some personal information may be exchanged with third parties in the normal course of business and indicates that you grant Cool Blackberry Themes permission to share the necessary information with third parties in order to conduct business with you. 

**Legal And Safety Factors**

We may disclose personal information if required by law (for example, to comply with a subpoena) or in the event that we need to share information with a third party in order to protect your safety and security or the safety and security of  Cool Blackberry Themes, its divisions, or its employees. 

**Changes In This Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy may change at any time. You should review this policy periodically to refresh your knowledge of our policy and to note changes that may have been made. We are committed to allowing you to control how your information is used, and if we plan to change our privacy policy significantly with regard to the sharing of your personal information, we will notify you 30 days in advance of the change during which time you may contact us with a request to change or delete personal information that we have stored, providing that this information is not required for normal business and accounting purposes. 

**Cool Blackberry Themes**

13506 Summerport Village Parkway, Suite 281 

Windermere, FL 34786 

We can be reached via email at [jennifer@coolblackberrythemes.com](mailto:jennifer@coolblackberrythemes.com) or you can reach us by telephone at 407-409-1262
